我好想朱莉
Man, I sure miss Julie.
西班牙侏儒
Spanish midgets.
西班牙侏儒摔跤
Spanish midgets wrestling....
朱莉  原来你是这么联想的
Julie! Okay, I see how you got there.
你知道电话是干嘛用的吗
You ever figure out what that thing's for?
我在过滤电话
I'm trying this screening thing.
如果我老去接电话  大家会以为我很闲
I figure if I always answer the phone, people will think I have no life.
老天啊  罗德里戈真是无往不胜
My God! Rodrigo never gets pinned!
听到哔声后  自觉留言吧
At the sound of the beep, you know what to do.
喂  我要找鲍勃
Hello. I'm looking for Bob.
我是洁德
This is Jade.
我不知道你的电话改了没有
I don't know if you 're still at this number,
不过我不断在想我们过去那段美好的时光
but I was just thinking about us, and how great it was,
我知道都已经三年了
I know it's been three years...
可是我希望我们能够重修旧好
but I was kinda hoping we could hook up again.
我差点没敢给你打这通电话
I barely had the nerve to make this call...
-你知道我做了什么吗   -什么
- ...so you know what I did? - What?
我喝得微醺
I got a little drunk...
还一丝不挂
...and naked.
我是鲍勃
Bob here!
你最近都在忙什么
So what have you been up to?
还是老样子
Oh, you know, the usual.
教健美操
Teaching aerobics...
整天参加派对
...partying way too much.
我还要告诉你
And in case you were wondering,
新007电影海报上那双腿是我的
... those are my legs on the new James Bond poster.
你等我一下  有另一通电话打进来
Can you hold on a moment? I have another call.
-我爱她  -我知道
- I love her! - I know.
-我回来了  -那我们到底要不要聚一聚
- I'm back. - So are we gonna get together or what?
当然要
Absolutely.
明天下午怎么样
How about tomorrow afternoon?
知道格林威治村的中央公园咖啡馆吗  五点左右
Do you know uh, Central Perk in the Village, say, five-ish?
-太棒了  到时见  -好的
- Great. I'll see you then. - Okay.
不错  这电话装的值了
Okay. Having a phone has finally paid off.
就算你装鲍勃装得很像
You know you do do a good Bob impression...
等她明天一看到你
I'm thinking when she sees you tomorrow...
就会发现你不是鲍勃本人了
...she may realize you're not Bob.
我只希望当她知道鲍勃放她鸽子的时候
I'm hoping that when Bob doesn't show up...
她会投向邻桌陌生人的怀抱
...she'll seek comfort in the arms of the stranger at the next table.
老天  你真是坏到骨子里去了
Oh, my God. You are pure evil.
坏到骨子里
Okay, pure evil...
欲求不满
... horny and alone.
我试过后者
I've done this.
对  大家都在
Yeah, everybody's here.
各位  跟新墨西哥的朱莉打声招呼吧
Hey, everybody! Say hi to Julie in New Mexico!
朱莉
Hi, Julie.
趁罗斯在讲电话
While Ross is on the phone...
每人交62块庆祝他的生日
...everybody owes me 62 bucks for his birthday.
你可不可以去个零头
Is there any chance that you're rounding up from...
差不多20块这样子
...you know... ...from like 20?
少来了  要有礼物  演唱会  还有蛋糕
Come on, we got the gift, the concert and the cake.
蛋糕也需要吗
Do we need a cake?
各位  我知道数目有点大
Look, guys. I know it's a little steep.
可是为了罗斯啊
But it's Ross.
为了罗斯
It's Ross.
好了  咱们待会儿见  我还得去
All right. Okay. See you later. I gotta go...
做件事
...do a thing!
好了  甜心  我晚上再打给你
Okay, sweetheart, I'll call you later tonight.
你不是真的要那么做吧  老兄
You're not really going through with this, are you?
我非做不可
You know, I think I might just.
你们晚上吃什么
What are you guys doing for dinner tonight?
我想我要开始为罗斯的生日存钱了
Well, I gotta start saving up for Ross' birthday.
我只好待在家里吃灰尘了
I guess I'll just stay home and eat dust bunnies.
怎么那么贵呢
Can you believe how much this costs?
你们有时候会不会觉得
Do you guys ever get the feeling that...
钱德勒和他们
... Chandler and those guys...
根本不明白  我们赚的钱没他们多
...don't get that we don't make that much money as they do?
对  他们总是说  咱们去这儿  去那儿
Yes. They always say let's go here, let's go there.
好像我们去得起一样
Like we can afford to go here and there.
对  而且我们总是得去个好地方  你知道吗
Yes, and we always have to go to, you know, someplace nice. You know?
我们连反对的权利都没有
And it's not like we can say anything about it,
因为这是为了生日
because this is a birthday thing...
为了罗斯
...and it's "for Ross."
-为了罗斯  -为了罗斯
- For Ross. - For Ross.
老天
Oh, my God!
我在上班
I'm at work...
我跟往常一样工作  切切切  煎煎煎
...just an ordinary day, chop, chop, saute, saute.
突然间  我们经理李昂叫我去他的办公室
Suddenly, Leon, the manager, calls me into his office.
原来他们开除了午餐大厨  你们猜谁顶上了
It turns out they fired the lunch chef, and guess who got the job?
如果不是你的话  那就太讨厌了
If it's not you, this is a horrible story.
幸好  就是我
Fortunately, it is me.
他们还升我为采购主任  感激不尽
And they made me head of purchasing,  thank you very much.
太棒了
That's so cool!
我刚在楼下碰见了罗斯和钱德勒
Anyway, I just ran into Ross and Chandler downstairs,
他们觉得我们该出去庆祝一下
and they think we should go out and celebrate.
去个好地方
You know, someplace nice.
Someplace nice.
你们觉得我的肾能卖多少钱
How much you think I can get for my kidney?
说真的  你不能这么做
I'm tellin' you. You can't do this.
要是走传统路线  我永远把不到那种尤物
Come on. I can't get a girl like that with conventional methods.
那有什么关系呢  她要找的是鲍勃
That doesn't matter. She wanted to call Bob.
鲍勃一定是她理想的对象
Hey, for all we know, Bob is who she was meant to be with.
你这么做或许会毁了两个人幸福快乐的机会
You may be destroying two people's  chance for happiness.
我们不认识鲍勃
We don't know Bob.
我们认识我  我们喜欢我  拜托  让我快乐起来
We know me. We like me. Please let me be happy.
你过去告诉那个女人实话
Go over there and tell that woman the truth.
好吧
All right.
快去
Go.
是这样  我要
Listen, I have to....
我要向你坦白一件事
I have to confess something.
什么事
Yes?
放你鸽子的人是混蛋
Whoever stood you up is a jerk.
-你怎么  -我不知道
- How did you - I don't know.
我有第六感  我就是这样  古怪而敏感
I just had this weird sense. But that's me, I'm weird and sensitive.
面纸
Tissue?
谢谢
Thanks.
不用  你留着用吧
No, you keep the pack.
我今天已经哭干了
I'm all cried out today.
这杯敬我刚刚被升为午餐大厨的老妹
Here is to my sister, the newly appointed head lunch chef.
现在还负责采购
Who is also in charge of purchasing.
恭贺她荣升为午餐大厨  还负责采购
Newly appointed head lunch chef who is also in charge of purchasing...
罗兰不在的时候  她还有自己的小办公桌
Who has her own little desk when Roland's not there.
午餐大厨  采购  罗兰不在时  有自己的小办公桌
Lunch chef, purchasing, own little desk when Roland's not there...
-敬我的老妹  -等等  我还有传呼器
- here's to my little sis... - Wait! And I got a beeper!
厉害
Cool.
没关系  我等好了
That's fine, I'll just wait.
抱歉
Sorry.
敬摩妮卡
Monica!
各位可以点菜了吗
Are we ready to order?
对不起  我们还没看菜单
You know what? We haven't even looked yet.
那你们看过之后再叫我
When you do, let me know.
我会在那边翘首以盼
I'll be over there on the edge of my seat.
看这些标价
Look at these prices!
是呀  跟抢钱似的
Yeah, these are pretty "cha-ching."
这些是什么  名牌鸡吗
I know! What are these, famous chickens?
-抱歉  我迟到了  恭喜你  摩妮卡  -谢谢
- Sorry I'm late. Congratulations, Mon. - Thanks.
我不后悔迟到  我跟洁德的午后约会太美妙了
I'm not sorry I'm late. How incredible was my afternoon with Jade?
从她在我答录机上给你的留言看来  的确很美妙
Well, pretty incredible according to the message she left you on my machine.
钱德勒  她为什么会在我的答录机留话给你呢
Hey, Chandler, why is this woman leaving a message for you on my machine?
我只能跟她说我的号码是你的号码
Oh, see, I had to tell her that my number was your number,
因为我不能跟她说我的号码是我的号码
because I couldn't tell her that my number was my number
因为她以为我的号码是鲍勃的号码
because she thinks that my number is Bob's number.
你再说一次  罗柏先生来电时我怎么办
Tell me again. What do I do when Mr. Roper calls?
可以点菜了吗
Do I dare ask?
好  我要先来一份生牛肉  然后再来一份烤虾
Yeah. I'll start with the carpaccio, and then the grilled prawns.
听起来不错  我也一样
That sounds great. Same for me.
那这位先生呢
And for the gentleman?
我要泰国鸡肉披萨
I'll have the Thai chicken pizza.
如果我的披萨不加干果和大葱什么的
But if I get it without the nuts and leeks and stuff...
会不会便宜点
...is it cheaper?
你觉得可能吗
You'd think, wouldn't you?
小姐呢
Miss?
好了  我想要点配餐沙拉
Ok, I will have the side salad.
那要配在什么菜旁边呢
And what would that be on the side of?
我不知道
I don't know.
你就帮我放在我的水旁边好了
Why don't you put it right here next to my water?
那你呢
And for you?
我想我要来一碗黄瓜汤  还有
I'm gonna have a cup of the cucumber soup and...
走好
...take care.
我要一份卡津鲶鱼
I will have the Cajun catfish.
还要别的吗
Anything else?
给我吟诵一首《温柔杀手》怎么样
Yes, how about a verse of "Killing Me Softly"?
你会朝我的鱼打喷嚏  对不对
You're gonna sneeze in my fish, aren't you?
加上小费  再除以六
Plus tip, divided by six....
好了  每个人给我28块钱
Everyone owes 28 bucks.
每个人
Everyone?
你说得对  对不起
Oh! You're right, I'm sorry.
谢谢
Thank you.
今天是摩妮卡的重要日子  她不用付
It's Monica's big night. She shouldn't pay.
谢谢
Thank you.
用五个人去除
So five of us is...
每个人33.5元
...33.50 a piece.
不行  抱歉  不可能
No. No way. Sorry, not gonna happen.
毕业舞会重演
Prom night flashback.
对不起  摩妮卡  你升了职  我替你高兴
Sorry, Monica. I'm feeling happy you got promoted...
可是冷黄瓜糊要三十几块
... but cold cucumber mush for 30-something bucks?
不行
No!
瑞秋只点了那盘小沙拉
Rachel just had that little salad...
乔伊只吃了片小得可怜的披萨
...and Joey with his teeny pizza!
好吧  菲比
Okay, Pheebs.
那我们就各付各的  好吗
How about we'll each pay for what we had?
小事一桩
It's no big deal.
你当然不当回事
Not for you.
到底怎么了
All right, what's going on?
算了  各位  我现在真的不想谈这事
Look, guys, I really don't wanna get into this right now.
这样只会让大家心里有疙瘩
It'll make everybody uncomfortable.
拜托  说出来吧
You can tell us.
对啊  尽管说吧  没关系的
Yeah, hello? It's us. We'll be fine.
我们三个
We three...
觉得
...feel like that...
你们有时候不太明白
...sometimes you guys don't get that....
我们没你们那么有钱
We don't have as much money as you.
好吧
Okay.
我懂了
I hear you.
我们可以好好谈谈
We can talk about that.
那么
Well, then...
我们就
...let's.
我想我只是从没想过钱是个问题
I guess I just never think of money as an issue.
-那是因为你有钱  -说得好
- Because you have it. - That's a good point!
你们以前怎么没提过这个问题呢
So how come you guys haven't talked about this before?
因为总是有事要庆祝  像摩妮卡升职
Because it's always something. Like with Monica's new job...
或是罗斯的生日狂欢
...or the whole Ross' birthday hoopla.
我可不希望我的生日让大家不开心
I don't want my birthday to be the source of any kind of negative....
你们要为我搞狂欢吗
There's gonna be a hoopla?
基本上有这项安排  事后还有一些东西
Basically there's the thing, and then the stuff after the thing
我们也可以不管那项安排
If it makes anybody feel better, then we can just forget the thing...
只送礼物就好了
...and we'll just do the gift.
礼物  礼物不就是那项安排吗
Gift? The thing's not the gift?
不  那项安排是一起去看混混与自大狂
No, the thing was, we were gonna go see Hootie and the Blowfish.
混混与自大狂
Hootie and the...
我可以到时听广播
I can catch them on the radio.
不  现在我愧疚了  你想去看现场演唱会的
No. Now I feel bad. You wanna go to the concert.
不  听着  这是我的生日
No, look. It's my birthday...
重要的是我们大家一起过
...and the important thing is that we're all be together.
-全部  -一起过
- All of us. - Together.
不是去演唱会
Not at the concert.
-好  谢谢  -谢了
- Okay, thank you. - Thanks.
那个依波拉病毒  被感染到一定很惨
So, the Ebola virus. That's gotta suck, huh?
天呐  摩妮卡  袋子里装的什么
Gee, Monica. What's in the bag?
不知道  钱德勒 咱们看一下吧
I don't know, Chandler. Let's take a look.
像在演滑稽短剧
Oh, it's like a skit.
是六人份的晚餐  有五块牛排
Why, it's dinner for six. Five steaks...
和一根给菲比的茄子
...and an eggplant for Phoebe.
我们餐厅换了肉食供应商
We switched meat suppliers at work,
新供应商送了我这些牛排谢我
and the new guys gave me the steaks as a thank-you.
等等  还有  钱德勒  那信封里还有什么
But wait, there's more. Chandler, what is in that envelope?
对了  刚才在外面排演时那没么蹩脚的
By the way, this didn't seem so dorky out in the hall.
是六张混混与自大狂的演唱会门票
Why, it's six tickets to Hootie and the Blowfish!
自大狂哦
The Blowfish!
算在我们头上  所以别担心  我们
It's on us. So don't worry. This is...
请客
...our treat.
谢了
So, thank you.
你们的热情哪儿去了
Could you be less enthused?
各位  你们是一番好意没错
Look, it's a nice gesture. It is.
可是我们觉得这像
But it just feels like....
像什么
Like?
施舍
Charity.
Charity?
我们只是想让大家高兴
We're just trying to do a nice thing here.
罗斯  可你们的好意让我们觉得我们这么渺小
Ross, you have to understand that your nice thing makes us feel this big.
事实上  是这么小
Actually, it makes us feel that big.
我不懂  我们怎样做都不对
I don't understand. We can't win with you guys.
你们觉得那么渺小的话  那或许不是我们的错
If you guys feel this big, maybe that's not our fault.
或许只是因为你们感觉有问题
Maybe that's just how you feel.
现在我们的感觉要你们来说了
Now you're telling us how we feel.
你看  我们根本就不该提这事的
Ok, we never should have talked about this.
我想我不去演唱会了
I'm gonna pass on the concert.
因为我现在不太有心情去混
I'm just not in a very "Hootie" place right now.
-我也是  -我也是
- Me neither. - Me too.
各位  我们票都已经买好了
Guys, we bought the tickets.
那你们就有空座放头冠什么的了
Then you'll have extra seats for all your tiaras and stuff.
你说这话的时候为什么盯着我看
Why did you look at me when you said that?
这下子我们都不能去了
So I guess now we can't go.
你们想去就去啊  我们非得集体行动不可吗
Do what you want. Do we always have to do everything together?
知道吗  你说得对
You know what? You're right.
很好
Fine.
好吧
All right.
我们会去的
We're gonna go.
不过还有六个小时  我们到时候再去
It's not for another six hours. We're gonna go then.
-钱德勒  -在
- Chandler. - Yeah.
天啊  你准备好了吗
Are you ready?
好了  等我先拿个外套  还有我今天上床了
Just let me grab my jacket and tell you I had sex today.
什么  你今天上床了
What? You had sex today?
从别人嘴里说出来感觉更酷
It sounds even cooler when somebody else says it!
我很厉害  我让她爽到咬住嘴唇才忍住叫声
I was awesome. She was biting her lip to stop from screaming.
我知道我很久没有这样了  但我认为这是好现象
I know it's been a while, but I took that as a good sign.
你还在过滤电话吗
Still doing the screening thing?
我今天上床了
I had sex today.
我再也不用去接那个电话了
I never have to answer that phone again.
听到哔声后  自觉留言吧
At the sound of the beep, you know what to do.
鲍勃  我是洁德  听着
Hey, Bob. It's Jade. Listen.
你那天放我鸽子  我难过极了
I wanted to tell you I was really hurt when you didn 't show up yesterday.
结果你知道吗   我认识了另一个人
And just so you know, I ended up meeting a guy.
我是鲍勃
Bob here.
你认识了别人
So you met someone, huh?
没错
Yes, I did.
事实上  我两小时前还跟他上床了
In fact, I had sex with him two hours ago.
那他表现怎么样
So how was he?
鲍勃  他跟你没法比
Oh, Bob, he was nothing compared to you.
我拼命咬住嘴唇才忍住没叫出你的名字
I had to bite my lip to keep from screaming your name.
很高兴听你这么讲
Well, that makes me feel so good.
他的技术太差了
It was just so awkward and bumpy.
或许是因为他用了些你不熟悉的新招式
Maybe he had some kind of new cool style that you're not familiar with.
你习惯就好了
You have to get used to it.
没多少时间让我去习惯了
There wasn 't much time to get used to it...
懂我的意思吗
...if you know what I mean.
我现在没心情看演唱会
You know what? I'm not gonna be able to enjoy this.
我知道  这是我的生日  我们该聚在一起的
I know. It's my birthday. We all should be here.
那就走吧
So let's go.
或许我们应该听一首再走
Well, maybe we should stay for one song.
对  现在离开对他们很不礼貌
Yeah. It would be rude to them for us to leave now.
说不定他们现在正玩得很开心呢
The guys are probably having a great time.
来吧  再猜一次
Come on, you guys. One more time.
好吧  —
Ok. One.
错了
Nooo.
-不可思议  -真棒  棒极了
- Amazing! - Excellent, that was excellent.
真不能相信他们错过了
I can't believe the guys missed it!
你说谁  哦对
What guys? Oh, yeah.
请问  你是盖勒摩妮卡  对吧
Excuse me. You're Monica Geller aren't you?
-我们认识吗   -你以前当过我的保姆
- Do I know you? - You used to be my babysitter.
天啊  小史蒂夫·费歇尔
Oh, my God! Little Stevie Fisher?
你现在怎么样了
How have you been?
很好  我现在是律师了
Good. I'm a lawyer now.
你不可能是律师  你才八岁
You can't be a lawyer. You're 8.
听着  很高兴见到你  我要去后台了
Listen. It was nice to see you. I gotta run backstage.
等等  后台
Wait, backstage?
他们是我公司代理的
My firm represents the band.
-我是罗斯  -我是钱德勒
- Ross. - Chandler.
你们想见见乐队成员吗
You guys wanna meet the group?
那走吧
Come on.
对了  你以前也跟我爸乱搞过吗
Are you one of the ones that fooled around with my Dad?
大家好
Hey, you guys!
生日快乐
Happy birthday!
谢谢  谢了
Oh, thank you. Thanks.
你们昨天晚上过得怎么样
How was your night last night?
无聊透顶  你们呢
Oh, well, it pretty much sucked. How was yours?
我们也觉得无聊透顶
Ours pretty much sucked too.
但是我碰到了小史蒂夫·费歇尔  还记得吗
But I ran into Stevie Fisher. Do you emember him?
记得  我当过他的保姆
Oh, yeah! I used to baby-sit him.
他爸好吗
Hey, how's his dad?
很好
Good.
除此之外  我们昨天整晚都很不顺
Aside from that, the whole evening was pretty much a bust.
对  我们很想念你们
Yeah, we really missed you guys.
对  我们刚才还说  这件事实在是太小儿科了
Yeah, we were just saying, this whole thing is so stupid.
我们绝不能
We just have to really, really not
让钱这种事影响
let stuff like money, get like
那是草莓印吗
Is that a hickey?
不  我只是
Oh, no, I just....
我跌倒了
I fell down.
跌在别人嘴上
On someone's lips?
你那草莓印哪里来的
Where'd you get the hickey?
派对或
You know, a party or
什么派对
What party?
也不算是派对  只能算是
It wasn't a party so much as a...
一群人聚在一起
...a gathering of people.
有吃的  有音乐  还有
With food and music and...
乐团
...and the band.
你们跟混混与自大狂狂欢了
You partied with Hootie and the Blowfish?
对  很显然史蒂夫跟混混是死党
Yes. Apparently, Stevie and Hootie are like this.
那草莓是谁种的
Who gave you that hickey?
是其中一个自大狂弄的
That would be the work of a Blowfish.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe it! I can't believe this!
我们呆坐在家里  猜乔伊的手指头
We're just sitting at home, trying to guess Joey's fingers...
而你们却跑出去狂欢作乐
...and you guys are partying and having fun and all:
还喊着  自大狂  吸我脖子
"Hey, Blowfish, suck on my neck!"
不要怪我们  本来你们也可以去的
Don't blame us. You could've been there.
什么  当接受你们施舍的穷朋友吗
What? As part of your "poor friends outreach program"?
这下可好  有公事  能借电话用吗
Oh, great. It's work. Can I?
我不晓得该说什么  很抱歉我们赚的钱比你们多
I don't know what to say. I'm sorry we make more money than you.
可我们不会因此感到愧疚  因为我们工作很努力
But we're not gonna feel guilty about it. We work really hard for it.
我们就不努力吗
And we don't work hard?
我是摩妮卡  我刚收到寻呼
It's Monica. I just got a page.
有时我们会想做比较花钱的事
It's just that sometimes we like to do stuff that costs a little more.
是我们拖你们后腿了
And you feel like we hold you back.
对  不对
Yes. No.
李昂  等等
Leon, wait.
各位
Guys!
我不明白
I don't understand.
那些牛排只是肉商送来的礼物
Those steaks were a gift from the meat vendor.
那不是回扣
That was not a kickback.
拜托  那我付钱给他们好了  这事就当算了
Come on. I'll just replace them, and we can forget the whole thing.
什么公司政策
What corporate policy?
不
No.
好  好的
Yeah. Okay.
我被开除了
I just got fired.
你们的帐单  一共4.12
Here's your check. That'll be $4.12.
我来付
Let me get that.
你有没有五块钱
You got 5 bucks?
听到哔声后  自觉留言吧
Here comes the beep. You know what to do.
是我
Hi, it's me.
听着  鲍勃  我可能要求过分了
Listen, Bob. I'm probably way out of line here.
都过三年了  说不定你另交女友了
It's been three years, and you 're probably seeing someone else now...
可看在我们以往的情分上  能不能共度一夜
...but if we could have one night together, for old time 's sake....
度过干柴烈火的一晚
One hot, steamy, wild night....